faster quicker mental strength you can
do
[Music]
this no you aren't in the moment lose
your sense of self and surroundings and
feel the motion be the motion never
forget the universe is always in motion
once you align with it that's when
you'll unlock skills you never knew you
had I haven't been to mysterium in
forever since way before the merge I'm
not even sure the Sorceress who created
me is still alive if she is she would
know the best way to protect you from
cuz if RZ gets a hold of you I'm sure he
plans to turn you back into a spell to
free the Forbidden five so it's really
our only choice what's bothering you
bonso the Sorceress she only knows me as
a spell what if she doesn't believe in
me as a real
person the Sorceress made everything
about you if anyone would believe in
your true self it's got to be her I I
guess look I know you all all love
adventure and danger and risking your
lives but me and the other finders
aren't exactly skilled Warriors like you
no problem Gio you spits and Fritz can
stay
here where'd they go
anyway uh-oh you sure we should do this
well it's do this or be bored just say
no to boredom hit
it amazing let's see if it
Spritz spit get out of there we'd love
to but we can't stop
[Music]
it me and not so so much to see Together
We will
rise
[Music]
weight
be got
[Music]
you good thing Sora stores my Elemental
Mech in the cave
missing
rules I'm thinking boredom would have
been less
[Music]
painful so jro here is going to fly us
all the way to mysterium that's the plan
zann can you give Jiro the directions I
cannot there are no trustworthy maps of
the post merged World in my databanks
but I'm sure bonsel knows how to get
there I haven't been to mysterium since
it was its own Realm I have no idea
where it is so no one knows where
mysterium
is still practicing your technique of
giving objects Spinjitsu
practicing and failing just like my
regular Spinjitsu
Aaron you have more natural Spinjitsu
Talent than anyone you heard what eold
said my Spinjitsu is unstable still as
wonky as it was when you met me I'm
going to get to oted to First Fang I
just know it as Master woo would tell me
patience young ninja but there isn't
time for patience the blood moon is
coming and if I can't learn Rising
Dragon
technique I shouldn't even be a ninja
that's nonsense maybe your path isn't
what you expected but like I've told you
you have the potential to be the
greatest of all the ninja I know and
that's a lot to live up
to I wish I had your confidence
I'm not feeling very confident these
days more
Visions I've never been so anxious I
have no idea when the Visions will come
and they just shut me down if I don't
find a way to stop them I won't be
present enough to lead us to confront
Ross I wish Master woo was here I bet he
never felt like this you can't dwell on
where you came from or where you're
going live live in the moment in this
drill you'll compete against each other
highest score wins highest score right
here not happening you're going
down me one you
Z you flinched 1 one
denied hey we're playing it like that
fine no you're not harmonizing with the
world you're fighting against it
frustrating each other
break isn't this annoying just doing
nothing I love doing nothing you're a
rock nothing is what you do but me I do
action I'm the most actionist ever being
injured is the
worst h
[Music]
it is too bad Aaron and Sora are not
here they are far more knowledgeable
about the crossroads than we are whoa
hey
there is it me or is trying to not draw
attention to ourselves just drawing
attention to ourselves it'd be bad if we
were recognized RZ Could Have Eyes
everywhere but someone's got to have a
map of the merged lands in this place
that place looks
promising we should not stop here the
owner is not trustworthy and if he
recognizes me we might be can I help you
fine
customers wait do I know you the odds of
that are statistically low given that so
many people call the crossroads
home well I suppose so then welcome
stranger we carry only the rarest
Treasures here can I interest you in an
authentic toothbrush of the Ancients
only used once
twice it smell is
unexpected that's just the scent of
authenticity my friend but I can tell
you're a Discerning gentleman would you
like to buy a disco
[Music]
toaster uh do you have any trustworthy
maps of the merged lands you've come to
the right
place here you go on the house for free
I have a drawer full of them use it in
Good
[Music]
Help such f RS they should have taken
the
toaster you are going to have some new
guests in fact I think you might know
them
already according to the map we should
follow this line over a huge
Lake not seeing a lake down there and
this Cloud wasn't on the
map not a normal cloud
poison
detected where are we jro can you fly us
out of here keeping
low he has been injured by the poison
well you were right there is definitely
no Lake here and no life either
master the basics fundamentals you got
this I know you didn't expect to train
little one but as you now know we Dragon
Masters are ninja ourselves you have
much
[Music]
potential Sora I sense you're
overthinking I know it's it's just I
feel like I'm doing everything backwards
I already have an elemental power but I
can't do Spinjitsu and it's a little
intimidating when your best friend is
some Spinjitsu Prodigy all living
creatures walk their own paths even
ninja I am the worst ninja trust me I've
met worse that does not help you put too
much pressure on yourself find some
calm if we don't learn Rising Dragon
technique We Can't Stop
RW and I'm the weak link on the team
here disturbing my privacy you humans
are all
alike hey I'm from a family of dragons
and you're like the only one I've ever
met who hates people I have my reasons
well I'm going to change your mind about
how great people can be just by existing
and being my awesome self H very few
humans have ever achieved Rising Dragon
you realize you are probably all wasting
your time if you really thought that you
wouldn't bother teaching
[Music]
us stuck in the middle of the desert
with no way
out I'm sorry bonsel about what I'm
supposed to be protecting you the
finders are like my family my other
family and right now I'm putting you
into more danger than even RW you're not
responsible for me Cole if I didn't want
to come I wouldn't have but this journey
was my idea and we can continue on it we
still have the
map the line is gone did that map change
were we given a trick map that no
account for Dulan I should have trusted
my memory
banks well we were headed north before
we hit that
cloud so if we still go that way we
should reach mysterium
right
begin don't mess this up
Don't Force It Aaron force and strength
were counter to the motion of the world
the universe has its own speeds you need
to align with again
[Music]
hold on
Aon
e oh no
[Music]
thanks
buddy whoa are you seeing this indeed if
we are all seeing it then it cannot be a
mirage come on maybe we'll find water or
even just some
shade move
what is that
thing and what does it want no idea but
I know what it's going to
[Music]
get in this weather your attacks are
probably just cool and refreshing cool
and refreshing was not my intention
[Music]
ow well at least we're
alive as alive as a spell can
be huh
are we on a stage oh
spended you're awake because the show is
about to begin I can't see out of the
eye not even sure if this type of injury
will heal I'm so sorry I messed this all
up for everybody I knew you weren't
ready child you're demoted down to First
Fang you'll be back in our group before
you know
it Ninja never thought I'd see the likes
of you
again are we supposed to know him I have
never personally met him but I believe
his name is
dorama oh you are not the ninja I was
hoping for no matter my revenge will
still be sweet since it was your kind
that ruined me ever since Imperium fell
I've been lost without purpose but then
I discovered this place the perfect
location for my next chapter D's Academy
for
ring huh it's not easy finding students
thankfully my old friend fulian and I
made a deal his fake Maps lead people to
my school and after I recruit them we
rehearse you mean capture them I said
recruit all day and all night we perfect
the art and craft of stage workk has he
always been this Preposterous well he is
a professional actor after my intensive
Hands-On Performance Academy you'll be
ready to entertain the world in my new
Ultimate stunt show if you survive that
is time to start
acting you're doing it all wrong I need
more fear in your eyes we have a lot of
rehearsal ahead of us but don't get
discouraged we all start somewhere look
at me we have to stop this I was never
the performer in my family and also I
don't want to be fried to grisp Imperium
Electro cage it will not let people
through so if we want to get out we have
to find a way to shut it down from the
inside
inform bunzel stay
back almost a spell perhaps we are not
protecting her she is protecting us I
didn't tell you to explore the space
stage
Manager Go Bo
all
get run it is too dangerous
here jro get them somewhere
safe no self-respecting school allows
the students to escape stop them
[Music]
a
you think you could dis destroy my stage
manager with just a second time I have
made
[Laughter]
upgrades yes now I'm buying your
performance you look absolutely
terrified
use that go with it I have an idea
follow
me oh this stunt show has so many twists
and turns all it's missing is a have
here what are you doing
[Music]
truly unpredictable finale no
notes you don't mind driving dama back
to the authorities can't wait to lock
them up need a lift thanks but we still
have work to do stay
safe guess we're off to mysterium
if we knew how to get there I may have
something I have been examining drama's
Imperium Tech dama had scanned the local
terrain creating a wealth of regional
Maps nice work Zane Jiro how you
feeling okay this is weird right is this
the right place this is mysterium
[Music]
how'd the monastery of Spinjitsu get out
here
[Music]